[
    {            
        "question": "Please translate to English: Shomen Geri", 
        "answers": ["Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Side Kick", "Blade Edge (Side Snap) Kick", "Knee Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Muwashi Geri", 
        "answers": ["Roundhouse Kick", "Front Kick", "Toe Kick", "Blade Edge (Side Snap) Kick", "Knee Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Yoko Geri", 
        "answers": ["Side Kick", "Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Flying Kick", "Toe Kick"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Sokuto Geri", 
        "answers": ["Blade Edge (Side Snap) Kick", "Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Side Kick", "Knee Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Hiza Geri", 
        "answers": ["Knee Strike", "Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Toe Kick", "Blade Edge (Side Snap) Kick"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Sokusen Geri", 
        "answers": ["Toe Kick", "Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Side Kick", "Blade Edge (Side Snap) Kick"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Tobi Geri", 
        "answers": ["Flying Kick", "Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Side Kick", "Backwards Kick"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Ushiro Geri", 
        "answers": ["Backwards Kick", "Front Kick", "Roundhouse Kick", "Side Kick", "Knee Strike"]
    },
    {            
        "question": "Please translate to English: Shoken", 
        "answers": ["One Knuckle Fist", "Fore Knuckle Fist", "Backfist", "Elbow Strike", "No-Knuckle Fist"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Hiraken", 
        "answers": ["Fore Knuckle Fist", "One Knuckle Fist", "Backfist", "Elbow Strike", "No-Knuckle Fist"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Wa-Uke", 
        "answers": ["To Accept", "To Decline", "To Defend", "To Receive", "To Adjust"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Bushiken", 
        "answers": ["Palm Strike", "Hammer Strike", "Wrist Strike", "Finger Strike", "Ridge Hand Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Nukite", 
        "answers": ["Spear Hand", "Ridge Hand", "Knife Hand", "Empty Hand", "Closed Hand"]
    },
    {            
        "question": "Please translate to English: Reiken", 
        "answers": ["Backfist", "Front Fist", "Closed Fist", "Palm Strike", "Hammer Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Empi-Uchi", 
        "answers": ["Elbow Strike", "Finger Strike", "Ridge Hand Strike", "Hammer Strike", "Knife Hand Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Haito-Uchi", 
        "answers": ["Ridge Hand Strike", "Knife Hand Strike", "Elbow Strike", "Finger Strike", "Hammer Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Shuto", 
        "answers": ["Knife Hand Strike", "Ridge Hand Strike", "Elbow Strike", "Finger Strike", "Hammer Strike"]
    },
    {            
        "question": "Please translate to English: Seiken", 
        "answers": ["Flat Fist Punch", "Backfist", "Closed Fist", "Palm Strike", "Hammer Strike"]
    },    
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Tutsui", 
        "answers": ["Hammer Strike", "Knife Hand Strike", "Ridge Hand Strike", "Elbow Strike", "Finger Strike"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Obi", 
        "answers": ["Belt", "Uniform", "Floor", "Gym", "Testing Area"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Gi", 
        "answers": ["Uniform", "Belt", "Floor", "Gym", "Testing Area"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Kiai", 
        "answers": ["Shout of Spirit", "Shout of Anger", "Shout of Power", "Shout of Pain", "Shout of Energy"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Sensai", 
        "answers": ["One who has gone before", "Karate Student", "Senior Student", "One who learns", "Karate Master"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Karate-Ka", 
        "answers": ["Karate Student", "One who has gone before", "Senior Student", "One who learns", "Karate Master"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Sanchin-Dachi", 
        "answers": ["Sanchin Stance", "Sanchin Style", "Sanchin Form", "Sanchin Application", "Sanchin Instructor"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Bunkai", 
        "answers": ["Application", "Example", "Forging of the Bone", "Empty Hand", "Clashing Hands"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Sempai", 
        "answers": ["Senior Student", "Karate Student", "One who has gone before", "One who learns", "Karate Master"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Muwate", 
        "answers": ["Turn", "Step", "Breath", "Punch", "Kick"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Karate", 
        "answers": ["Empty Hand", "Closed Fist", "Clashing Hands", "Self Defense", "Forging of the Bone"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Kumite", 
        "answers": ["Clashing Hands", "Empty Hand", "Closed Fist", "Self Defense", "Forging of the Bone"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Kotekitae", 
        "answers": ["Forging of the Bone", "Empty Hand", "Closed Fist", "Self Defense", "Clashing Hands"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Kiba-Dachi", 
        "answers": ["Horse Stance", "Cat Stance", "Crane Stance", "Dragon Stance", "Tiger Stance"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Please translate to English: Butokukai", 
        "answers": ["Martial Virtue Gathering/Association", "Collection of Martial Arts Dojos", "Like Minded Students", "Martial Arts Competition", "Martial Arts Head School"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year was the Uechiryu Butokukai founded?", 
        "answers": ["1984", "1966", "1969", "1974", "1988"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did Mr. Durkin begin training?", 
        "answers": ["1966", "1984", "1969", "1974", "1988"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did Mr. Durking receive his black belt?", 
        "answers": ["1969", "1984", "1966", "1974", "1988"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did Mr. Durkin open his first dojo?", 
        "answers": ["1974", "1984", "1969", "1988", "1966"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year was the Atkinson Dojo built?", 
        "answers": ["1988", "1984", "1969", "1974", "1966"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Where was Mr. Durkin's first dojo located?", 
        "answers": ["Salem, NH", "Pepperell, MA", "Atkinson, NH", "Lexington, MA", "Hollis, NH"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What rank is Mr. Durkin?", 
        "answers": ["10th Dan", "9th Dan", "8th Dan", "7th Dan", "6th Dan"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What rank is Judy Durkin?", 
        "answers": ["9th Dan", "10th Dan", "8th Dan", "7th Dan", "6th Dan"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "Why is Judy Durkin's rank significant?", 
        "answers": ["First woman to achieve a master rank", "She beat Mr. Durkin to master rank", "First woman allowed to practice", "First female dojo owner", "First woman to earn blackbelt"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did George Mattson begin training?", 
        "answers": ["1956", "1958", "1966", "1969", "1874"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did George Mattson receive his black belt?", 
        "answers": ["1958", "1911", "1991", "1948", "1874"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year was Kanbun Uechi born?", 
        "answers": ["1877", "1911", "1991", "1948", "1874"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "How many kata are there in Uechi Ryu?", 
        "answers": ["8", "5", "12", "3", "13"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What are the three primary kata?", 
        "answers": ["Sanchin, Seisan, Sanseiryu", "Sanchin, Seiryu, Sanseiryu", "Seiryu, Seisan, Sanseiryu", "Kanchin, Seisan, Sanseiryu", "Sanchin, Kanchin, Sanseiryu"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What does Sanchin mean?", 
        "answers": ["3 Conflicts (Mind, Body, Spirit)", "3 Animals (Dragon, Crane, Tiger)", "Half Hard, Half Soft", "Mind over Matter", "3 Positions of Attack and Defense"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What does Seisan mean?", 
        "answers": ["13 Positions of Attack and Defense","36 Positions of Attack and Defense", "13 Stances", "36 Stances", "3 Conflicts"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What does Seisan mean?", 
        "answers": ["36 Positions of Attack and Defense","13 Positions of Attack and Defense", "13 Stances", "36 Stances", "3 Conflicts"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year was Kanei Uechi born?", 
        "answers": ["1911", "1877", "1991", "1948", "1874"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did Kanei Uechi die?", 
        "answers": ["1991", "1877", "1911", "1948", "1874"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year did Kanbun Uechi die?", 
        "answers": ["1948", "1877", "1911", "1991", "1874"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What year was Shushiwa born?", 
        "answers": ["1874", "1877", "1911", "1991", "1948"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What are the 3 animals of the Uechiryu style?", 
        "answers": ["Dragon, Crane, Tiger", "Scorpion, Crane, Tiger", "Dragon, Scorpion, Tiger", "Dragon, Crane, Panther", "Panther, Crane, Scorpion"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What was the style of karate that Uechiryu was originally known as?", 
        "answers": ["Pangai-noon", "Shushiwa", "Butokukai", "Ryokoryu", "Tomoyose"]
    },
    {                
        "question": "What does the original style from whch Uechiryu was derived mean?", 
        "answers": ["Half Hard - Half Soft", "3 Conflicts (Mind, Body, Spirit)", "Dragon Style", "Crane Style", "Tiger Style"]
    }
]